https://www.cornwall.ac.uk/college-governance/cookie-policy/

Cookie Policy
This cookie statement was last updated on 4th June 2020 and applies to citizens of the United Kingdom.
1. Introduction
Our websites, https://www.cornwall.ac.uk, https://www.duchy.ac.uk, https://www.bicton.ac.uk, https://www.falmouthmarineschool.ac.uk and https://www.ccbtraining.co.uk (hereinafter: “the websites”) uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our websites.
2. What are cookies?
A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of our websites and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.
3. What are scripts?
A script is a piece of programme code that is used to make our websites function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.
4. What is a web beacon?
A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.
4.1 Manage your consent settings
5. Cookies
5.1 Technical or functional cookies
Some cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.
5.2 Advertising cookies
We do not use any advertising cookies on this website.
5.3 Social media buttons
On our websites we have included buttons for Facebook, Twitter and Instagram to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook, Twitter and Instagram. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook, Twitter and Instagram themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.
Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook, Twitter and Instagram are located in the United States.
6. Placed cookies
WordPress
We use WordPress for website development. Read more
NameRetentionFunctionFunctional  wordpress_test_cookienoneChecks if cookies can be placedwordpress_logged_in_*persistentKeep users logged in
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
Google Tag Manager
We use Google Tag Manager for website statistics. Read more
NameRetentionFunctionStatistics  uslk_inital_urlpersistentuslk_referrerpersistentuslk_operator_bindingpersistentuslk_dragpersistentuslk_in_service_timepersistentuslk_page_impressionspersistentuslk_ssessionuslk_e1 year
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Tag Manager Privacy Policy.
YouTube
We use YouTube for video display. Read more
NameRetentionFunctionMarketing/Tracking  GPSsessionStore location dataFunctional  VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE6 monthsEstimate bandwidthStatistics  YSCsessionStore a unique user IDPREF1 yearTrack visits across websites
Sharing
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Policy.
Facebook
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
NameRetentionFunctionMarketing/Tracking  actppresence1 yearManage ad display frequency_fbc2 yearsStores last visitfbm*1 yearStore account detailsxs3 monthsStore a unique session IDfr3 monthsEnable ad delivery or retargeting_fbp3 monthsTrack visits across websitesdatr2 yearsProvide fraud preventionsb2 yearsStore browser details*_fbm_1 yearStore account detailsFunctional  wd1 weekDetermine screen resolutionact90 daysKeep users logged inc_user90 daysStore a unique user IDcsm90 daysProvide fraud preventionpresencesessionTrack if the browser tab is active
Sharing
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Policy.
Twitter
We use Twitter for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
NameRetentionFunctionFunctional  local_storage_support_testpersistentLoad balancing functionalityMarketing/Tracking  metrics_tokenpersistentStores if the user has seen embedded content
Sharing
For more information, please read the Twitter Privacy Policy.
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
7. Your rights with respect to personal data
You have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this cookie statement. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO)).
8. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookies
You can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.
Please note that our websites may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.
9. Contact details
For questions and/or comments about our cookie policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:
The Cornwall College GroupData Protection Officer,Cornwall College,Tregonissey Road,St Austell,Cornwall,PL25 4DJUnited KingdomWebsite: https://www.cornwall.ac.ukEmail: dpo@cornwall.ac.ukPhone number: 0330 123 2523
This cookie policy was synchronised with cookiedatabase.org on 4th June 2020
Related Pages
Anti-Slavery & Human TraffickingAppointing New GovernorsBoard Reports & Board MinutesCollege CharterCompliments & ComplaintsCurrent GovernorsEquality & DiversityFreedom of InformationPrincipal’s WelcomeSubcontracting & Supply ChainYour Information & Privacy Policy
